

Maksym Khaiuk

Middle Front End Developer

Hi, i am 33 years old web developer, living in Odessa, Ukraine. Qucik learning and highly responsible person with 2 years of commercial experience in Front End Development. Looking for a remote full-time job. Interested in learning and using new web technologies and services.

Mobile: +3 8 (063) 167 88 30

Email: khaiuk.maksym@gmail.com

Telegram: https://t.me/subarumax

Work Experience

Middle Front End Developer • Magic Powered

May 2021 - June 2023

My first IT company. Mainly developing blockchain crypto-related web apps and landing pages.

My responsibilities:

- developing mainly the front end part of web apps using React/Next.js framework with TypeScript;
- optimization;
- fixing bugs;
- CEO optimization;
- working as part of a team or independently;
- integration with REST API/web3;
- communication within a team (designers/PM/backend/devops);
- rare communication with clients;

Expirience: Junior Dev(6 months), Middle Dev (1.5 year).

Company website: https://magicpowered.io/

2nd Officer • Zodiac Maritime LTD.

June 2008 - July 2020

My ex-job was seaman, working in a UK-based company, world wide, with mixed crew on board bulk carriers.

Expirience: Deck cadet/study(3 years), 3rd officer(5 years), 2nd officer (4 years).

Company website: https://www.zodiac-maritime.com/





Education

August 2020 - April 2021

Hillel IT School and Self Study

Front-End Pro course

Sep 2008 - Jun 2010

Odessa Maritime Colledge

Navigation

Skills				
Dev Languages	Frameworks	Libraries	Other	Languages
JavaScriptTypeScript	ReactNext.jsStrapiMJML	 Axios Lodash Framer Motion Moment.js SASS Recharts Swiper Classnames React Hook Form Near API JS Wagmi WalletConnect Google Analytics 	 NodeJS GIT Github Bitbucket Gitlab AWS Figma Docker Clickup 	 English(B1) Ukraininan Russian